[
  {
    "userId": "2",
    "winnerId": "5",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "a-1770876069083-6dl4",
        "question": "Who played Nacho in Nacho Libre?",
        "options": [
          "Lauro David Chartrand-DelValle",
          "Jack Black",
          "Rosenda Hernandez",
          "Armando Tapia"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "id": "d-1770876069083-1g33",
        "question": "Who directed Nacho Libre?",
        "options": [
          "Hayao Miyazaki",
          "Brian De Palma",
          "Jared Hess",
          "Conrad Vernon"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 2
      },
      {
        "id": "c-1770876069084-tkv7",
        "question": "Héctor Jiménez played which character in Nacho Libre?",
        "options": [
          "Motivational Coach",
          "Esqueleto",
          "Monk #1",
          "Pro (Coliseo) Referee"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "id": "a-1770876069084-j6h2",
        "question": "Who played Chancho in Nacho Libre?",
        "options": [
          "Rosenda Hernandez",
          "Agustin Rey",
          "Darius Rose",
          "Armando Gaytan"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 2
      },
      {
        "id": "a-1770876069084-cytp",
        "question": "Who played Juan Pablo in Nacho Libre?",
        "options": [
          "María González",
          "Luis Garcia Rendon",
          "René Campero",
          "Moisés Arias"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
      }
    ],
    "createdAt": "2026-02-12T06:01:09.084Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": "2",
    "winnerId": "5",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "c-1770876072537-stnr",
        "question": "Héctor Jiménez played which character in Nacho Libre?",
        "options": [
          "El Pony",
          "Elderly Monk",
          "Muñeco",
          "Esqueleto"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
      },
      {
        "id": "a-1770876072536-fmrl",
        "question": "Who played Juan Pablo in Nacho Libre?",
        "options": [
          "Darius Rose",
          "Brett Chan",
          "Albert M. Madrid",
          "Moisés Arias"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
      },
      {
        "id": "y-1770876072536-vety",
        "question": "What year was Nacho Libre released?",
        "options": [
          "2007",
          "2006",
          "1983",
          "2001"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "id": "a-1770876072536-1vye",
        "question": "Who played Chancho in Nacho Libre?",
        "options": [
          "Armando Tapia",
          "Rodolfo Garcia Merino",
          "Moisés Arias",
          "Darius Rose"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
      },
      {
        "id": "c-1770876072537-7nfe",
        "question": "Darius Rose played which character in Nacho Libre?",
        "options": [
          "Peasant Woman",
          "Usher",
          "Chancho",
          "Emperor"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 2
      }
    ],
    "createdAt": "2026-02-12T06:01:12.537Z"
  }
]